(Howard:)No, but I did go
to the International Space Station.
(Girl:)Did you fly the rocket?
(Howard:)No, but I was in the rocket.
(Howard:)- I didn't actually...
- So you just flew around?
(Girl:)That's kind of like my uncle.
A flight attendant.
No, heh, I'm an American hero,
your uncle brings people nuts, okay?
All right, all right, all right.
(Leonard:)Boy, we are learning a lot here, huh?
Thank you, Astronaut Howard.
(Leonard:)Um, I am what's called
an experimental physicist.
Which is super fun because I get
to test theories and work with lasers.
(Leonard:)- Yes?
- How did you decide to become a scientist?
Oh, excellent question.
(Leonard:)Um, I suppose I've always been into science.
(Leonard:)My mother and father are scientists,
so I was kind of led in that direction.
(Leonard:)Pushed might be a better way to describe it.
(Leonard:)To be honest with you guys, when
I was your age, I wanted to be a rap star.